cssdeck.com 2017-11-19

# None

**Your privacy is critically important to us.**   
We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, newsletters, develop our products, or protect our rights. 

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, CSSDeck collects personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. CSSDeck also collects email address, usernames and code snippets that are uploaded to CSSDeck. Code snippets that are uploaded to CSSDeck are considered open source. CSSDeck also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. CSSDeck uses cookies to help CSSDeck identify and track visitors, their usage of CSSDeck website, and their website access preferences. CSSDeck visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using CSSDeck's websites, with the drawback that certain features of CSSDeck's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, CSSDeck may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in CSSDeck’s sole discretion. CSSDeck encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

## Third Party Advertising

Some of the advertisements you see on the Site are selected and delivered by third parties, such as ad networks, advertising agencies, advertisers, and audience segment providers. These third parties may collect information about you and your online activities, either on the Site or on other websites, through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies in an effort to understand your interests and deliver to you advertisements that are tailored to your interests.
